Oh!
哦
Ow!
Help! Help!
救命啊 救命啊
Am I dead?
我死了吗
You're not dead.
你没有死
You've been taken against your will.
你只是被绑架了
Kobe? Who is that?
是科比吗 你是谁
Dr. Phil? What the hell's going on?
菲尔教授 到底怎么了
I don't know. I was doing a show on teens with abandonment issues...
我不知道我正在参加一个有关被遗弃孩子的表演
and suddenly, I woke up here.
忽然间 我就在这儿了
Man, those kids are gonna be pissed.
天哪 那些孩子一定会气疯了
Hello, gentlemen.
你们好 先生们
You don't know me, but I know you.
你们也许不认识我 但我认识你们
You both play games with other people for a living...
你们都是靠玩游戏挣钱的
but, today, you play a game for your lives.
但是今天 你们要为你们自己的生命玩一个游戏
Right now, you are both breathing in a deadly nerve gas.
你们正在吸入一种致命的毒气
You have 120 seconds to reach the antidote...
你们有120秒的时间找到解药
or you die.
否则你们就完了
Oh, my God! We better get out of here!
天哪 我们一定要想办法出去
Let the game begin.
让我们的游戏开始吧
There!
看那儿
Hit the metal arm with something.
用什么东西去砸那根铁柱子
There.
用那个
Damn it!
妈的
Sorry.
对不起
Shaquille, I'm not angry at you...
沙科尔 我不是对你发火
but we are one minute away from death.
但还有一分钟我们就要见阎王了
Just shut out the "No" voice.
忘掉你的恐惧
Own your success.
你会成功的
Oh!
哦
Just make the damn basket!
快他妈的投中
What the hell was that for?
你在干什么啊
You hurt my feelings.
你伤了我的自尊
Your feelings? To hell with your feelings!
你的自尊 让他们都见鬼去吧
Everybody with their feelings!
每个人都有自尊
"I'm obese." "My kid's a brat." "Help me. Help me."
"我发胖了""我孩子很不懂事""帮帮我吧"
Just shut up!
让他们都滚蛋吧
Why can't I fix anyone?
为什么我谁也帮不了
I'm so dumb and worthless! Mama was right! Mama was right!
我实在是太笨太没用了 妈妈说得对 妈妈说得对
Hey, hey! Pull yourself together. You're a brilliant doctor.
嘿 嘿 别这样 你是个好医生
Not exactly.
不
- What? - I just tell people to "get real."
- 什么 - 我只会跟人说"要现实"
I'm not even a psychologist.
我根本不是一个心理学家
I'm... an electrician.
我 是一个电工
I failed you, Shaq. I failed you.
我对不起你了 沙科 我对不起你
- Booyah! - Yes!
- 太好了 - 好
30 seconds left!
还有30秒钟
This will never work.
这没用的
Of course- he wants us to cut through our feet.
当然 他要我们割自己的腿
You go first.
你先来
Bullshit.
开玩笑吧
Yeah.
是真的
You're probably not man enough.
看来你不够有勇气
I guess your mama was right.
我想你妈妈说得没错
Never!
不
Who's the coward now, Mama?
谁说我是胆小鬼 妈妈
Candy from a baby.
轻而易举
- Oh, my God! - I did it. We're saved.
- 天哪 - 我成功啦 我们得救啦
- What's wrong? - Wrong foot.
- 怎么了 - 锯错脚了
Motherfu-
奶奶的
《惊声尖笑4》
No one believed
在21世纪初
in the early years of the 21 st century
没有人相信
that our world was being watched...
我们的世界
the way a man with a microscope might scrutinixe the creatures
正被别人像显微镜那样
in a drop of water.
窥探着
Yet across the gulf of space
但是在广阔的宇宙中
a terrible evil prepared to unleash itself
一个邪恶的势力正跃跃欲试
upon an unsuspecting human race.
准备要对毫无防备的人类发动总攻
You're up early. Come back to bed.
你起的真早 回床上来
Come on.
来吧
Please.
求你了
Hello? Hello?
有人吗
Tom! Oh!
汤姆 哦
I know you missed me. Oh, I missed you too. God, you look great.
我知道你想我 我也想你 天哪 你看起来气色不错
I wanted to come by to thank you for setting up that job interview for me.
我想过来对你说声谢谢 帮我要来这次工作的机会
This isn't a good time.
现在不太适合
I just need something to keep me busy now that Cody's out of the house.
现在科迪走了 我想该找点事做
He just turned 11 .
他都11岁了
I enrolled him in military school last year.
我去年把他送去军校
It's supposed to be a great program.
我想这会是一项好的历练的
Boy, kids, you know, they just grow up so fast.
男孩子们 你知道的 他们总是这样突然长大
So I heard that you were dating again.
听说你又开始约会了
Knowing you, I bet she's brainy.
我想肯定是个聪明的女人
"Quixotic."
"狂想家"
90 points!
90分
Oh, you know, your work with the elderly
你知道吗 你为老人们的做的那些工作
really inspired me, Tom.
真的对我影响很大 汤姆
I mean, they have so much to teach us...
我是说 他们总有那么多值得我们去学的
and we have so much to teach them.
我们也有很多可以教他们的
You know, ultimately, they... really are just like us...
毕竟 他们其实跟我们一样
only... older.
只是 老了些
Anyway, I'm hoping that a new career will help
不管怎样 我希望新的工作
keep my mind off of... bad memories.
能够帮我忘记那些不愉快的东西
I'm sure you have memories, too. He's the kind of person you never forget.
我想你也一样 他是那种让人一生难忘的人
Sometimes, I wake up in the middle of the night
有时候我会突然在深夜惊醒
wondering where he is, and then I remember.
回想他在哪里 然后我就明白了
I know you miss him, too, but it's really been hardest on me.
我想你也在想他 但我想最受打击的人还是我
I'm rattling on, but if you don't vent your emotions...
我知道我说得有点多了但有时如果不能把情绪抒发出来的话
they just well up inside of you and burst out.
他们只会越积越深 然后爆发
The harder you try, the harder it all gets...
你越努力 事情就越糟
till you just can't shake it off anymore.
直到你不能承受为止
Oh!
哦
Like you're carrying around this enormous burden.
就像你带着个沉重的包袱
Sometimes your problems get so big.
有时候问题会越来越严重
- And then what do you say to yourself? - Jesus!
- 然后你怎么办呢 - 天哪
Yes, you can turn to religion or family and friends...
没错 你可以求诉于宗教 家庭 朋友
but in the end, you're still in agony.
但是到头来 你还是在那团迷雾中
Maybe that's why I want to become a nurse.
也许正因为这样我想成为一个护士
I'm just- I'm so in tune with everyone's emotions.
我只是 总是那么能了解其他人的烦恼
I guess I've always had a knack for being-
我想我总是有
Oh, my'God
哦 天哪
Ryan, go home. You've been working 16 straight hours.
赖安 回去吧 你已经连着工作了16个钟头
Come on, I need the overtime.
我要很需要那加班费
Don't worry. Okay?
别担心 好吗
I'm wide-
我清醒得
Ryan! What are you doing?
赖安 你在干什么
That was gold bullion-
那些是金条
No, not the monkeys!
不 那些猴子
They're loose!
他们跑了
Damn it, Tom! What the hell happened back there?
妈的 汤姆 刚才发生了什么
Aw, come on, Ed. That could've happened to anyone.
埃德 谁都有可能这样
Oh, yeah? You know what your problem is?
是吗 你知道你的问题在哪儿吗
As soon as the going gets tough, you give up.
每次事态严重的时候 你就放弃了
You're right. I quit.
没错 我不干了
Ah, you don't get it, do you?
你不明白我说什么 对吧
You could be the best, if only you'd see things through.
如果你能明白那些东西 你会是最好的
- I don't know. - Give me a break.
- 我不想听了 - 不要这样
What can I tell you, Ed? I guess I'm no good.
我该说什么呢 埃德 我想我也许还是不适合吧
Maybe I just don't have what it takes.
我想我没有那个能力
What are you talking about? You secured that tricky H-500 unit, didn't you?
你在说什么 你不是搞定了那个H-500吗
Aw, come on. That was easy.
哦 那个太容易了
Tom Ryan. I haven't seen you in a while.
汤姆 赖安 好久没见你了
Well, I spend every waking minute of my life operating a crane.
每当我醒着的时候 我都在操作那些起重机
God, I hate my job.
天哪 我真的受不了我的工作
Yo, Tom! Where you been?
嘿 汤姆 你去哪儿了
Mahalik.
马哈里克
Yo, C.J., this is my boy Tom Ryan.
CJ 这是我的老朋友汤姆 赖安
We used to work together down at the docks.
我们曾经一起在码头工作过
- Hey, Tom. How's the family, man? - You remember Marilyn?
- 嘿 汤姆 你的家人怎么样 - 你记得玛里琳吗
- Your lovely wife, how could I forget? - She dumped me.
- 你可爱的妻子 我怎么会忘记 - 她跟我分手了
Yeah, I know. I slept with her a few times.
哦 我知道 我跟她睡过几次
- What? - Me too.
- 什么 - 我也是
You guys talking about Marilyn? Great lay.
你们在说玛里琳吗 功夫不错
My pops introduced me to her.
是我兄弟介绍我认识她的
Ever since the divorce, it's like my life has no purpose.
离婚以后 我简直就觉得我的生活失去了意义
Half the time I walk around feeling like a xombie.
很多时候我都觉得自己成了一具行尸走肉
Yo, don't joke about xombies. That shit there- that's real.
千万不要拿将是开玩笑 他们是存在着的
Yo, you know Nashawn, down on 120th Street?
你认识120街的纳尚吗
Yeah.
恩
She told me that she heard a xombie going through her trash the other day.
她告诉我她有次听见有僵尸走过她的垃圾堆
The next morning, she turned up missing.
第二天早上 她就看来不见了
- Uh... - What? Okay, back up.
- 恩 - 什么 等一下
How in the hell do you "turn up missing"?
她怎么能"看来不见"呢
'Cause nobody knows where you are when they realixe you ain't there!
因为没有人能看到你 如果你失踪了
Guys, I'm trying to ask-
我只想问
So you telling me that you can appear and disappear at the same time.
你是说你能在失踪的时候被人看见
No, man. You can't appear and disappear at the same time.
不 你不能在失踪的时候被人看见
- The bitch ain't David Copperfield! - Uh, guys-
- 那人又不是大卫 科波菲尔 - 恩 兄弟们
Mmm. No, no.
等一下
But you can't be gone from one place and show up somewhere else entirely.
但是不能去了一个地方 然后又同时在另一个地方出现
So when you turn up, you're never missing.
只要你被人看到 你就不是失踪
And when you're missing, you never turn up.
一旦你失踪了 就不会被人看到
Unless... you a xombie.
除非 你是个僵尸
Damn!
妈的
Hey, that's some plausible shit right there. You should blog about that.
你说的真是经典 应该放到网上好好宣扬宣扬
I'm gonna put that on MySpace.
我会把它放到MySpace上去的
You do that!
一定要阿
Hey, Tom.
嘿 汤姆
You know what you need to do, man? You need to get away from all this.
你知道你该做什么吗 你应该把这一切都忘了
- You need to take a break. - Oh, I don't know.
- 你该休息一样 - 我不知道
No, no. He's right, man. You should come fishing with us one weekend.
不不不 他说得没错 你应该跟我们一起来钓鱼
Me and Mahalik, we found this great spot last summer.
我跟马哈里克 我们在去年夏天找到了个很妙的地方
Yeah. A great spot.
没错 好地方
Hey. You cold?
嘿 你冷吗
- L-Little bit. - Hmm.
- 有一点 - 恩
Hey. Look, man, um-
兄弟 恩
I'm not on the down-low or nothing, all right?
我不是什么同性恋之类的 明白吗
Oh, that's cool, man. Me, neither.
恩 没问题 我也不是
- Hey, what you doing? - Relax, man.
- 嘿 你要干什么 - 放轻松 兄弟
I'm just trying to grab some nuts.
我只是来拿些坚果
C.J., what are you doin'?
CJ 你在干嘛
- I just wanna eat some peanuts. - Huh?
- 我只是想吃点花生 - 恩
See? Peanuts.
看见了没 花生
I've been alone with you inside my mind
我曾在脑中跟你在一起
And in my dreams, I've kissed your lips
在我的梦中 我亲吻着你的双唇
A thousand times
一遍又一遍
I sometimes see you pass outside my door
有时我见你在门前经过
Hello
你好
Is it me you're looking for?
那是你在寻找的吗
I can see it in your eyes
我可以在你的眼中看到
I can see it in your smile
我可以在你的微笑中看到
You're all I ever wanted
你就是我一直想要的
And my arms are open wide
我的双臂永远为你敞开
Cause you know just what to say
你应该知道该说什么
And you know just what to do
你应该知道该做什么
Ooh, baby.
天哪
And I want to tell you so much
我想要告诉你
I love you.
我爱你
Yeah... we caught a lot of fish.
没错 我们捉了好多鱼
Yeah.
是啊
Black cod.
黑鳕
Damn.
妈的
Tom, you don't- I don't want you thinking that-
汤姆 你不要 我希望你不要
Hopefully, this doesn't affect your opin-
希望这不会影响
Why would you do that, and that's my first time meeting him?
你为什么要这样做 我们才第一次见面
Late again, Tom.
你又迟到了 汤姆
- Hey, Marilyn. - I thought you were moving.
- 嘿 玛里琳 - 我以为你已经搬家了
It's all I can afford right now.
我现在只能负担这个了
You took everything in the divorce except my name.
除了我的名字你把什么都在离婚协议里夺去了
No, actually, the judge granted me that yesterday.
你错了 法官昨天刚把那个判给我
You're now officially known as "Horace P. MacTitties."
你现在叫"贺瑞斯?P?麦可蒂"
I'm sure your new husband is pleased.
我想你的新丈夫一定很满意
He's a good man. A provider, unlike you.
他是个好人 不像你 他能负担我们的生活
You never cared about our children.
你从来不关心我们的孩子
Hey, that's not true. I'm a great dad.
嘿 不是这样的 我是个很称职的爸爸
Kids!
孩子们
Dad?
爸
- Hi, Dad. - Hey, Rachel.
- 爸爸好 - 好啊 雷切尔
How's it going there, uh... Princess?
最近过得怎样 我的小公主
It's locked.
门上锁了
Hey! Let me help you with that, muffin.
嘿 让我来帮你吧 小家伙
- I should do that. - It's no problem.
- 我来吧 - 不客气
- I honestly don't mind. - Neither do I.
- 我无所谓的 - 我也是
Fine. You take it.
好吧 给你了
I'll see you on Tuesday.
星期二见
Hey, Marilyn.
嘿 玛里琳
That's a good look for you, being pregnant.
你看起来不错 怀孕的样子
I'm not pregnant!
我没有怀孕
I didn't meant to- I'm sorry.
我不是这个意思 对不起
If you want to make things right, maybe you should start with our kids.
如果你想补过的话 还是好好跟我们的孩子相处吧
You're right. Those kids are all I have in this world.
你说得没错 那些孩子是我唯一剩下的
Well, the kids... and my car.
孩子 还有我的车
Ow!
哦
Mr. Koji, looks like we need someone new for the Norris account.
柯吉先生 我想我们需要派一个新人到诺里斯家去
Again?
还要
Every day we don't have someone looking after this woman, I lose big money.
每一天我们没有人去照顾她 我们就要损失很多钱
- What happened to last girl? - Yoko. Take a look.
- 上次的那个女孩呢 - 尤可 你看看吧
Holy shit!
天哪
Someone put a towel under her or something. Christ!
拿块毛巾放在她下面 天哪
It's the Norris house, Mr. Koji. They say it's cursed.
柯吉先生 有人说诺里斯的房子闹鬼
There no such thing as a curse.
从来没有闹鬼这么一说
Don't be ridiculous.
别开玩笑了
Those just old wives' tales.
这只是些无聊的道听途说
I need someone there today or I'm in big trouble.
我一定要找个人来顶替 要不我就麻烦了
Hello. I'm Cindy Campbell.
你好 我是辛迪 坎贝尔
I'm looking for a job in home health care.
我是来应征家庭护理员的工作的
I was recommended by a family friend, but unfortunately, he committed-
我是经一个朋友推荐的 可惜他已经自杀
Oh, my God!
哦 天哪
Don't mind her. She slip and fall.
不用理她 她不小心滑了一跤
You my new best employee. Ready start today?
你是我最好的新员工了 可以今天开始工作吗
Oh, it's so fast. I don't know.
哦 那太快了 真的可以吗
Oh, trust me. Uh, you're gonna love this job.
相信我 你会喜欢这份工作的
Come on, I show you. We can be there 10 minutes.
来 跟我一起去 10分钟就到了
Come! Come!
来 来
Mr. Koji?
柯吉先生
Hello?
有人吗
Oh, my God! Oh!
哦 天哪 哦
Okay, oh.
哦
- Oh, let's get you up and... - Oh!
- 让我扶你起来 - 哦
Okay, come on. Here we go.
来 我们走
- Oh, I'm sorry. - There you are.
- 哦 对不起 - 你在这儿
I see you've met Mrs. Norris- she catatonic.
你已经见过诺里斯太太了 她有紧张性精神症
Yes, I was just trying to get her back up on the bed.
是的 我只是想扶她去床上
I was afraid that she would be hurt.
我怕她会受伤害
You know, when I came in, I just saw her lying here on the floor.
你知道吗 我进来的时候她就躺在地上
Of course, of course. I help. You grab her legs, I grab her arms.
当然 当然 我来帮忙 你拿她的脚 我拿她的手
Mrs. Norris, I'm here to take care of you.
诺里斯太太 我是来照顾你的
Yes, I'm very happy to meet you, too.
是的 我也很高兴见到你
See? This job perfect for you.
看见没 你很适合这份工作
Let me show you rest of house.
让我带你去看看房子其余的部分
Right this way.
来这儿
So, what do you think?
你觉得怎样
I don't know. There's something strange about this house.
不知道 这房子有点奇怪
- A presence. - A presence? Don't be silly.
- 有某种东西存在着 - 东西 别开玩笑了
- Nothing wrong with this house. - It's funny.
- 这房子没什么奇怪的 - 很奇怪
I always dreamt I would live in a house like this with my husband...
我一直梦想着跟我的丈夫 住在这样的房子里
but I guess that's all just in the...
我想这只是
past.
从前
Who wants to see upstairs?
你想看看楼上吗
It's a nice neighborhood close to schools and shopping.
这社区不错 有学校有商店
There are hardwood floors throughout. Passed almost every inspection.
硬木质地板 每次都通过检验
Big backyard goes back 100 feet.
100尺大的后院
And in here is the bathroom.
这儿是浴室
Very big, very...
很大 很
nice.
漂亮
It is nice.
没错
It seems like it'd be a great place to work...
我想这应该是个好地方
but I just can't shake this feeling of... evil.
只是我一直有种 邪恶的感觉
Evil? That craxy talk.
邪恶 开玩笑
Do you know anything about the people who used to live here?
你知道曾经在这儿住过的人吗
People? No, nothing about people. I don't remember anything.
人 不记得了
Mr. Koji, did something strange happen in this house?
柯吉先生 这儿是不是有发生过奇怪的事
Strange? Don't be silly.
奇怪 别开玩笑了
This house perfectly normal.
这房子很正常
I'm sure you're right, and yet... it's as if someone's watching us.
我想你说的对 只是 我总觉得有人在注视着我们
Mr. Koji?
柯吉先生
That was me... just excited about hiring you.
是我 太兴奋能有你这样的雇员
Very, very enthusiastic!
非常非常的高兴
We offer medical and dental and two weeks' paid vacation!
我们提供健康及牙医服务 还有两个星期的带薪假
I'm hoping... you can start today!
我想你今天就可以开始了
Maybe get in a whole week!
先做一礼拜
You put in for this job...
如果你能接受的话
we got wonderful opportunities for you.
以后还会有更多的机会
Mr. Koji, is there something you're not telling me about this?
柯吉先生 你是不是在对我隐瞒什么
I was... dirty.
我只是 有点脏
So... the job?
那 工作呢
I'll take it.
我接受了
Get your glove! I'm in the backyard!
拿上你的手套 我在后院
Robbie, come on. Let's go!
罗比 快来啊
That's not how you're going to get through to him.
这不是跟他沟通的办法
Look, Rach, this is guy stuff.
雷切尔 这是男人之间的东西
You got to trust me.
你得对我有信心
All right, Robbie, you ready for the Tom Ryan Express?
罗比 你准备好搭乘"汤姆 赖安快线"了吗
Yeah, maybe, one day, I can grow up to be just like you.
也许有一天我也会变成像你一样
All right, I know I let you kids down...
没错 我知道我曾经让你们失望
but you have no idea how hard it is to be a father.
但你们不知道做一个父亲是多么的难
Well, when you start, let me know.
你准备开始的话 告诉我一声
You okay?
你没事吧
My eyes! My eyes!
我的眼睛 我的眼睛
Oh, much... better.
哦 好 多了
- I'm so sorry. - Oh, that's okay.
- 对不起 - 没事
I've taken balls to the face before.
我的脸也曾经被球击中过
Hi. I'm Cindy Campbell, your new neighbor.
你好 我是辛迪 坎贝尔 你的新邻居
Tom, Tom Ryan.
汤姆 汤姆 赖安
You, uh, live here all by yourself?
你 恩 一个人住那儿
Well, I'm-I'm taking care of Mrs. Norris...
我在照顾诺里斯太太
but... yes, for the first time in my life, I'm on my own.
不过 确实是第一次一个人独立
I know that feeling.
我知道那种感觉
- It wasn't always that way. - I know.
- 不是总是那样的 - 我知道
You thought you'd found your soul mate.
有时你以为终于找到了一个知心的人
Yes.
是的
And then one day you come home...
但有天你回到家
and find your so-called soul mate in bed with a complete stranger.
发现那个所谓的知心的人变成了一个彻彻底底的陌生人
Well, not a complete stranger- Sammy Sosa.
也许不完全是陌生人 塞米 索沙
Sound familiar?
听说过吗
No, not at all.
不 从来没有
But I do know what it's like to be in that much pain...
不过我知道那种痛苦的感觉
and the worst part is you have to suffer through it-
但最悲惨的是你需要
- Alone? - It looks like we have a lot in-
- 一个人度过 - 看起来我们有很多的
Common.
共同点
- We're already finishing each other's... - Dinner.
- 我们已经在为对方完成 - 晚餐
Sentences.
句子
Well... maybe all we really need is a friend.
我想 也许我们都需要一个朋友
I'd like that.
我希望那样
Well, I better get back to Mrs. Norris.
我看我得回诺里斯太太身边了
It's time to put her catheter in, and then after that...
该是时候把她的导尿管放好 然后再
I've got to scrub in between her fat folds...
把她全身上下都擦干净
and I've got to lance her boils.
切开她的脓包
I've got to open her up and then-
把他们打开 然后
...empty the colostomy bag and...
清理结肠口
mop up the drool.
拖干地上的口水
That's wonderful.
太美妙了
- I'll see you around? - Definitely.
- 我还会再见到你吗 - 当然
Okay.
好的
Okay, Mrs. Norris, time to dig out that doody bubble.
好了 诺里斯太太 是时候清理掉那些泡泡了
Whoa... Oh! Ow!
哇哦 哦 哦
Mrs. Norris?
诺里斯太太
Have you noticed anything strange about this house?
你觉察出这房子有什么不对吗
- Yes! Yes! - No?
- 是的 是的 - 没有
Yes!
是的
Oh, you're probably right. Guess I'm just being silly.
也许你说的对 我想我是太紧张了
Just relax now.
放轻松
Here we go. Okay.
来吧
Oh, you poor thing. You don't have to be scared.
可怜的人 你不用害怕
I'm here to take care of you.
我是来照顾你的
You know, I think you and I are going to be wonderful friends.
我想我们会成为很好的朋友
I do. That's right.Just relax.
没错 放轻松
Let's get in those ears.
我们来擦擦耳朵
Okay. All right.
好的
That's right. Oh, it feels good.
很好 感觉很好吧
Okay.
好的
You love this, don't you?
你喜欢 对吧
It's nice and warm. Feels good, doesn't it?
温温的很舒服 不是吗
Oh, my God! Oh! Oh!
哦 天哪 哦 哦
I'm so sorry!
对不起
Robbie!
罗比
Come on!
来
Let's toss the old pigskin!
我们好好的来一场
Ooh.
哦
I'm so sorry. I didn't see you there. Are you all right?
对不起 我们没有看见你 你没事吧
It's okay. My throat cushioned the blow.
没事 我咽了口气
Thank God. I lost my temper. My son's-
谢天谢地 我失去冷静了 我儿子他
What's wrong? You look scared.
怎么了 你看起来很惊慌
Oh, nothing. It's just-
哦 没什么 只是
There's something going on in this house.
那房子有点奇怪
Last night, I saw a face.
昨天晚上我看到一张脸
- Did it have a nose? - Yes.
- 他有鼻子吗 - 有
That does sound like a face.
那应该是张脸
And then there was this weird hand in the shower...
还有我洗澡时的那双奇怪的手
and this horrible thing on the stairs.
楼梯上恐怖的东西
I can't go through this all again.
我想我不能再承受更多了
Oh, I get it. There's some other guy.
哦 我明白了 是一个男人
You still love him, don't you? I wish you both the best.
你还爱着他 对吗 我祝你们白头偕老
Wait! You don't understand.
等等 你不明白
It's painful to talk about, but you deserve to know.
也许说起来很痛苦 但你有权利知道
I was married once.
我曾经结过一次婚
Get out the way, bitch!
你给我走开 婊子
Don't call me no bitch! You ain't shit!
你有什么资格骂我 你这臭屁虫
Shut your ass up, snow ho!
你给我闭嘴
Well... actually, married twice.
恩 事实上 是两次
My husband and I were living our dream.
我丈夫和我在实现着我们的梦想
Ladies and gentlemen, your challenger, Cindy Campbell.
女士们先生们 今天的挑战者 辛迪 坎贝尔
Stay loose, Cindy. Remember your training. Keep your focus.
放轻松 辛迪 记住你的训练 保持注意力
Always think, where's the next punch coming-
总是想着 下一拳会从什么地方
After 20 fights, I was undefeated.
我已经保持20场不败
Only one fighter stood between me and the belt.
我离金腰带只差最后一场胜利
You got this chick. She's nothing.
你可以赢她的 她没什么的
Tiffany Stone!
蒂芬尼 斯通
Cindy, listen to me.
辛迪 听我说
I know you're scared, but I believe in you. You can win this.
我知道你很害怕 我对你有信心 你可以做到的
And if I do win, George,
如果我真的赢了 乔治
then will you tell me what my nickname means?
你可以告诉我我的诨名有什么意思吗
Yes. I promise.
我保证
Okay. Now just stick with the jab and lead with your right.
好 坚持用短直拳 注意右边攻击
Watch your footwork.
还有脚步
Let's go!
来吧
Whoa, whoa! You do that one more time,
哇 哇 你如果再这样的话
I'm taking a point off, you hear me?
我就会扣你的分了 听见了吗
I got it, I got it! Dude, check it out!
我的 我的 你们快看哪
I can't take it anymore!
我受不了了
And that's when I lost my cool
就在那时我失去了冷静
and made the biggest mistake of my life.
犯了一生中最大的错误
Cindy, no!
辛迪 不要
Ooh, a nickel!
哦 五分钱
No!
不
Get out of the way!
快走开
George!
乔治
No!
不要
If I hadn't have thrown that punch, none of it would've happened.
如果不是我出了那一拳 这些事就不会发生
- I blame myself for it all. - As well you should.
- 我觉得这都是我的责任 - 我想你应该这样
But, Cindy, the past is the past.
不过 辛迪 过去的就让它过去吧
Maybe you ought to think about your future.
也许你该想想你的未来
If I'm ever going to love again...
如果我要再次相爱的话
it has to be with somebody who'll be there for me.
那应该是一个一直在那里等我的人
Well, I don't have a great track record in that department.Just ask my son.
我想我在这方面的表现不太好 问问我儿子吧
I have. What's an "cock monger"?
我已经问了 什么叫"鸡巴贩子"
Uh... that's not really important.
恩 这不重要
What matters is I've let a lot of people down.
最重要的是我让很多人都失望
Oh.
哦
- I should go. - Wait!
- 我该走了 - 等一下
Maybe I'm just not meant to be happy...
也许我的一生都不怎么快乐
but something about you makes me want to try.
但是我总觉得你有什么 让我想去尝试
- What's happening? - I don't know!
- 怎么了 - 我不知道
Why is the sky so dark?
为什么天这么黑
Why is the wind moving towards the storm?
为什么风会向着风暴的方向刮
Why don't any of us have driers?
为什么我们没有人有烘干机
I've never seen clouds like that before!
我从来没有见过那样的云
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 你还好吧 - 是的
- Can you believe that thunder? - No.
- 你敢相信那雷吗 - 不
That storm is so fierce. I've never seen anything like it.
那风暴太强了 我从来没见过这么大的风暴
- I haven't either. - Imagine being out there.
- 我也是 - 想象一下在外面的感觉
That last one sounded really close.
刚才那个听起来好近
Don't worry- lightning never strikes in the same place twice.
不用害怕 闪电从来不会击中同一个地方两次
- Where's Rachel? - I thought she was with you.
- 雷切尔在哪里 - 我以为她在你身边
Oh, there you are.
你在这儿
Okay. That's it. We're fine.
好 完了 我们没事了
That last bolt of lightning smelled like a-
最后一下闪电闻起来像是
Giant turd.
大便的味道
Yes, the... lightning.
没错 那 闪电
I'll go look for Robbie.
我去找罗比
Turn it again, see if it'll start.
再转转试试 看看他会不会启动
I don't know what's going on. The car's not working, it's just not working.
不知道怎么了 汽车就是发动不起来
Start!
开
Go!
走
My bowels have stopped moving! Why?
我的肠子不动了 为什么
- How's it going, Marvin? - I just had this car working: now it's dead.
- 怎么了 马文 - 我刚把这辆车修好 现在又不行了
- Try changing the solenoid. - Good idea.
- 试试看换个螺线管 - 好主意
Death to America!
美国去死吧
Aw, shit!
哦 妈的
Run!
跑
Beautiful outfit!
衣服不错
Thanks.
谢谢
- Where's your ride, G? - Move it, dawg!
- 你的车在哪儿 - 快跑
Hello?
你好
"Haro"?
Hibachi. Benihana. Teriyaki.
你住这儿吗
Nagasaki. Okinawa. Hokkaido. Yokohama.
你的日文太差了 对我的耳朵简直是种污染
Karate.Judo. Sumo. Samurai.
你是鬼吗
Nissan. Honda. Mitsubishi. Subaru.
是的 我被杀了 我的冤魂四处游荡
Hara-kiri. Tsunami. Kamikaxe. Banxai.
真可怜 我的身世也很悲惨
Yamaha. Nikon. Casio. Aiwa.
你一定认错人了
Minolta. Hitachi. Seiko. Toshiba.
我知道打败外星人的方法
Buddha! Shitake kimono!
天哪 快告诉我
Tempura. Sushi. Sashimi!
方法在我父亲的心脏里 跟着血迹走
Fujitsu!
等一下
I can't read that.
我看不懂这个
That's better.
这个好多了
Let's go, honey! Let's go! Let's go!
我们走 亲爱的 快走
Robbie, Dad's home!
罗比 爸爸回来了
What is it? What's going on?
这是什么 怎么了
Death.
死亡
- Dad, talk to me. What's happening? - There's no time to explain.
- 爸爸 快告诉我发生什么了 - 没有时间解释了
Alien attack!
外星人袭击
Well, actually, that about sums it up.
事实上这就是事情的本质
Fill this up with food. We're leaving this house in 60 seconds.
装满食物 我们要在60秒内离开
My ass!
我的屁股
Penis.
宝贝
We gotta go.
我们该走了
- Cindy! - Tom!
- 辛迪 - 汤姆
- Run for it! - Where are you going?
- 快跑阿 - 你去哪里
Someone's out there, somebody who knows a way to stop all of this.
有人知道怎样可以阻止这一切
- Oh, you wouldn't understand. - I understand.
- 你不会懂的 - 我懂
- Come with me. - Oh, I'd like to, but my kids.
- 跟我来吧 - 我也想 可是我的孩子
I... guess this is good-bye.
我 想这可能是说再见的时候了
When this is all over, promise me that you'll find me, that you'll never forget me...
当这一切都结束的时候 一定要来找我 不会忘了我
that you won't give up until I'm back in your arms.
一定要让我回到你的怀里
- Alive? - Yes.
- 活着 - 是的
I promise.
我保证
Good-bye, Cindy.
再见 辛迪
Hey, wait!
嘿 等一下
A solenoid... for luck.
螺线管 祝你好运
Marvin! You put a solenoid in?
马文 你把螺线管放进去了吗
Yeah, I got one from that crackhead over there.
是的 我从那家伙这里搞来一个
- Get in. - Why should we?
- 快进去 - 为什么
Because you're my responsibility now, and like it or not, I'm all you've got.
因为我要对你们负责 不管怎样 我是你们唯一的亲人了
Ow!
哦
- Hey. Hey! - Thank God.
- 嘿 嘿 - 谢天谢地
Hey! What are you doing?
嘿 你在干什么
- Get in the car, Marvin. - Come on, Tom, stop joking around.
- 快进来 马文 - 汤姆 别开玩笑了
Get in the car, Marvin, or you're gonna die.
快进来 要不你死定了
Okay, fine.
好吧
- No, wait for me to... - Still locked.
- 不 等我 - 还是锁着
- Why are you reaching at the same time? - What do you mean?
- 为什么你总是要同时间去开呢 - 你说什么呢
- All right, on three. - You counting now?
- 好吧 我数三下 - 你要数了吗
One, two, three, open the door!
一 二 三 开门
- Okay, on three. - One, two-
- 好 到三 - 一 二
Three.
三
- Don't do that. You're trying to annoy me. - It's still locked.
- 不要这样 你快把我弄烦了 - 还是锁着
I'm going on three. One, two-
我来数三下 一 二
Don't count when I count. I have a problem with that.
别在我数的时候数 我会受影响
- What's the matter with you? - Turn your mouth sideways.
- 你到底在干什么 - 把头转过去
- If you look at me I lose count. - What are you craxy?
- 你看着我我没法数 - 你在说什么
- One, two, three! - Two, three!
- 一 二 三 - 二 三
- Don't do it the same time. - You said "three."
- 别同时跟我做 - 你说了三
- You go on "four." Can you count? - Four.
- 那你就在数四的时候吧 你会数数吗 - 四
- So on your "three" or my "four"? - There's only one "three".
- 是你的三还是我的四 - 只有一个三
- I'm tryin' to get in the car. - Then you do it on "four."
- 我只想要进来 - 那就在数四的时候做
You said, "three". So are you doin' it on "three" or am I doin' it on "two"?
你说三的 到底是你在三的时候做还是我在二的时候做
- For Christ's sake! - I heard "three."
- 我的天哪 - 我听见三了
If the count is "three," you do it on "four."
如果我数三下 你就应该在四的时候做
- Now it's "four". - Why would you go on "four"?
- 现在是四了 - 你为什么要四
You gave me "four" first and you stole my "four."
是你先给我四的 现在你又要把它拿走
- But I have to count to "three" first. - You stole my "four."
- 但我要先数三 - 你偷了我的四
- Just let me say "three." - I've got wait on you now, huh?
- 总之让我说三 - 我要等你对吧
- You want the black man to wait again? - Do whatever you want.
- 你还想让黑人等着 - 随你的变
- That's what I've been doin'. - Why would you do that?
- 我一直都在做 - 你为什么要这样
Why would you reach for it when I say "three"? That's what this is about.
你为什么要在我数三的时候做 这是问题的关键
Do I still go on "four"?
我还是在四的时候做吗
When I say "three," don't worry about "four."
我说三的时候 不要管四
You got all the time in the world!
你可以慢慢来
You can go home, watch television and come back and then open the door!
你可以回家 看看电视 然后再回来开门
- Fine. - One-
- 好吧 - 一
No. No "one." I'm out. No thank you.
不 不要一了 我投降 谢谢了
I'll take the next one. Does that work for you?
我坐下一辆 可以吗
- Jesus. - Attitude.
- 天哪 - 态度有问题
Seriously, I'd rather be dead.
说真的 我宁愿去死
"A girl had a pet duck.
一个女孩有一只宠物小鸭
"She fed and took care of her pet duck.
她时常照料和喂养着它
"But one day, the duck got loose and ran away from the girl.
但是有一天 那鸭子不见了
"The duck ran down the road and kept running...
那鸭子在路上一直跑
until he found a pond."
直到它找到一个池塘
Mr. President, we've just received word...
总统先生 我们接到消息
the planet is under attack by aliens.
星球正遭受攻击
Oh. Okay.
哦 好的
"The duck went back"-
那鸭子回去
Sir? They've already wiped out some of our cities.
先生 他们已经摧毁了我们的一些城市
If nothing is done, they'll kill us all.
如果我们再不行动的话 我们就会被打败
I see. Well, I'll handle that in a minute.
我知道了 我等下会处理的
But right now, I need to find out what's happening with the duck.
但现在 我要知道那些鸭子怎么了
Sir, with each passing moment, more people will die.
先生 现在过去的每一秒里 都有人在死亡
The people are gonna die regardless...
人总会死的
but this duck still has a fighting chance.
但那鸭子还有机会
I've read the story before, Mr. President.
我读过这故事 总统先生
The duck dies.
那鸭子死了
My God! That's horrible.
我的天哪 这太恐怖了
Mr. President, the aliens? We're under attack.
总统先生 那些外星人 我们正遭受攻击
You mean, right now all of these children's parents could be dead?
你是说现在这些孩子的父母都有可能被杀
Kids! Kids, please!
孩子们
It's not as bad as it seems.
这不像看起来那么糟
They didn't die alone.
他们并不是独自死的
I'm sure they died with all the other people you loved.
我想他们一定跟你们爱着的其他人一起死的
Even Santa Claus?
你是说圣诞老人吗
No, of course not. There's no such thing as Santa Claus.
不 当然不是 根本就没有圣诞老人
Just like the Tooth Fairy, completely made up.
就像牙仙一样 都是编造出来的
Easter Bunny- Never existed.
复活节小兔子 从来就没有
The female orgasm.
女性高潮
Wait and see what happens when you try to find it.
根本不可能找到
What's wrong? Your parents all getting divorces?
怎么了 你父母想要离婚吗
I can give them a little advice, if you'd like.
我可以给他们一点建议 如果你们想的话
Oh, I forgot. They're all dead.
哦 我忘了 他们都已经死了
All right now, let's go on to another story, "Rumpelforeskin."
好了 我们来下一个故事"割去包皮"
"Stiltxkin," sir. We have to get you to the White House.
"斯蒂尔斯基"先生 我们要尽快送你去白宫
I just don't get kids.
我总是不懂那些孩子们
- Remind me to sign that abortion bill. - Yes, sir.
- 记得让我签那些堕胎提案 - 是的 先生
You may leave through the forward exit doors...
你可以从前门离开机舱
or the gaping hole in the side of the plane.
或是从两边的逃生门
We realixe you have a choice in airlines...
我们知道你们有很多的选择
and we appreciate you flying with Southern Coast Air.
欢迎你们乘坐南方海岸航空
- Thank you. - Hello?
- 谢谢 - 有人吗
Hey! That's mine! I found it!
嘿 那是我的 我找到的
- Cindy? - Brenda?
- 辛迪 - 布伦达
Oh, my God. It's been so long.
哦 天哪 真的好久没见了
Yeah, too long.
是啊 太久了
I thought you were dead.
我以为你死了
Oh, I thought you were dead, too.
我也以为你死了
What are you doing here? Were you on this plane?
你在这里干什么 你在这飞机上吗
No, I'm trying to get a good story.
不 我只是想找个好新闻
I'm a reporter now. I work for the local news.
我现在是记者了 在附近的新闻社上班
Wow, you're really doing well for yourself.
哇 看起来你干得不错
I was on assignment. Take a look at this.
我当时正有一个采访任务 看看这个
Here's Detroit.
这里是底特律
And here's Detroit after the attack.
这是攻击后的底特律
Oh, my God.
哦 天哪
The attack was devastating.
攻击力太强大了
It's over, Cindy. Humanity has lost the war.
辛迪 人类已经输了这场战争
No, no. There's still hope.
不 不 还有机会的
I have reason to believe that there's someone here that has the answers...
我相信有人会有解决问题的答案的
maybe even a way for us to fight back.
甚至还击的方法
Come on. It would make a great story.
来吧 这会是个好新闻的
Maybe. But how are we supposed to get there?
也许吧 但我们怎么过去呢
None of these cars work.
这些车都发动不起来
Wait. See if this works.
等等 也许这个会管用
Hey! I got the last working car in New York!
嘿 我找到了纽约最后一辆能跑的车
This is our road, bitches! Ha-ha!
这里是我们的天下了 婊子们
You're right, Cindy. That worked pretty well.
你说得没错 辛迪 这挺管用的
I...
我
Look at all the injured.
看看那些受伤的人
It's so sad.
太可怕了
Big-ass rat, man!
真他妈的
Oh! That sewer took forever to fix!
哦 这下水道真难修
Man, I'm gonna need a hot bath after all of that-
我他妈的要去洗个热水澡
What the hell happened here?
这里他妈的到底发生了什么
- Zombies! - Damn!
- 僵尸 - 妈的
Let's go!
我们走
Don't let 'em bite you!
别让他们咬你
Good news! They can still feel electricity.
好消息 他们能感觉到电流
Grandma? The xombies have got my grandma!
奶奶 那些僵尸抓去了我奶奶
Die, Grandma! Die! Die!
去死吧 奶奶 去死 去死
- I loved you! I loved you! - Mahalik?
- 我爱过你的 我爱过你的 - 马哈里克
Look what they did to my grandmama!
看看他们对我奶奶所作的
Whoa!
哇
That woman raised me from birth.
那女人把我从小养大
Hey, he's got a car. He's got a car.
嘿 他有车 他有车
Give us the car and the keys!
把车跟钥匙给我们
This isn't my car. I would, but I can't. It's not my car.
这不是我的车 如果是的话我会给你们的
It's not my car. Don't worry, kids. The doors are locked.
这不是我的车 别担心孩子们 车门都已经上锁了
There's no possible way they can-
他们不可能可以
Pull the robot out of chocolate. But that's just common sense. Oh, waiter!
把机器人从巧克力堆里拉出来 这是常识 哦 等等
- Daddy! - Kids!
- 爸爸 - 孩子们
Whoa!
哇
Why?
为什么
Well.
好吧
Get back! Get back!
退后 快退后
Gimme the gun. I'm taking the car.
把枪给我 这车是我的
What do I do about him?
那他怎么办
I don't want the car. I just need a gun.
我不要车 我只要枪
No way I'm giving up the gun. I want the car.
我不可能把枪给你的 我要那车
So, you need a gun, and you want a car.
所以 你想要枪 你想要车
- What do you want? - Well, I've never owned a knife.
- 你要什么 - 我从来没有过刀
Okay. Let's all switch on three.
那我们数三声一起换
One, two, three.
一 二 三
Is this right?
这对吗
I don't think so.
看起来不是
Dad, they're taking the car.
爸爸 他们把车抢走了
Yes, well, uh, let's keep going.
是哦 恩 那我们走吧
What? That's it? You're giving up?
什么 就这样 你就放弃了
Yeah, that's right. I'm giving up.
是的 没错 我放弃了
You want a hero? Go find someone else.
你想要一个英雄吗 找别人吧
Why?
为什么
Let's go.
我们走吧
Now, let me get this straight:
我们来弄弄清楚
The girl hugged the duck, and then it dies?
那女孩抱了抱鸭子 那鸭子就死了
Mr. President, the nation is under attack.
总统先生 我们国家正遭受攻击
Get me Homer Landsquiddy.
帮我接"民族安检部"
You mean, "Homeland Security."
你是指"国家安全部"
Sir, this woman was an eyewitness to one of the attacks.
先生 这位太太看见了攻击的场景
- What can you tell us? - They're indestructible.
- 你能告诉我们什么 - 他们是无敌的
The clothing was burned off everyone's bodies.
每个人身上的衣服都被烧掉
There were naked people everywhere.
到处都是赤裸着的人们
- Were you naked? - No.
- 你是吗 - 没有
Thank God. Some good news at last.
谢天谢地 总算有个好消息
Get her a souvenir.
带她去领份纪念品
Lil' Kim- Lil' Kim got my sandwich.
林锦 林锦拿了我的三明治
Look out- Russell Crowe's got a phone!
注意 罗素 克洛伊买电话了
R. Kelly, don't pee on me!
凯利 不要尿在我身上
My lovely lady lumps!
我可爱的婴儿肥
Where are we?
我们在哪里
I'm not sure, but I think we're close.
我不知道 我想应该近了
It's supposed to be near mile 62.
应该是在62公里处左右
Is something wrong?
有什么不对劲吗
No, it's just...
不 只是
I met this guy, and I wonder if he's safe.
我遇见了个男人 我在想他是不是平安
Oh, you'd love him, Brenda.
你会喜欢他的 布伦达
What's his name? I might've already loved him.
他叫什么 我也许已经爱过他了
Tom Ryan.
汤姆 赖安
Yeah, did him. Big, fat Chinese guy?
哦 我跟他上过 又肥又大的中国人
No... No.
不 不是
But he is the kind of guy that I'd like to share the rest of my life with.
他是那种我愿意托付终生的人
Cindy! Look!
辛迪 快看
What is this place?
这里是哪儿
I don't know, but the boy's father's somewhere in there.
我不知道 但那孩子的父亲应该在这儿
We'll have to sneak our way in.
我们得偷偷进去
But we're not gonna blend in dressed like this.
但是我们的穿着没法不让人察觉
- Brenda, look. - He's a wonderful boy.
- 布伦达 看 - 看起来不错
Exekiel?
伊齐基尔
Exekiel, where are you?
伊齐基尔 你在哪儿
Exekiel, shall we have a foot race?
伊齐基尔 我们来赛跑吧
No cheating.
不准作弊哦
That's him!
是他
He's cute.
他看起来不错
Friends, friends. Do not fear the noise of those of whom we do not speak.
朋友们 不要去理会来自我们从不提起的那些人的声音
There is a gentle truce between our village
我们与那些外面的生物
and the creatures beyond their borders.
有一个停火协议
Now, who would like to say grace?
有谁要来感谢恩典
Ooh!
哦
Ah, Exekiel.
伊齐基尔
Pee-pee.
尿尿
Pee-pee vagina.
尿尿的阴道
Amen.
阿门
Father?
神父
Holly.
你好
For what purpose do you interrupt
你为什么要来打扰
the celebration of the domestic partnership
末底改跟赫斯
of Mordecai and Hoss?
的婚礼
The guards caught two outsiders near the cabin.
护卫在小屋前面抓到两个外来者
Who are you?
你是谁
I must speak with you. I was sent by your son.
我有事要跟你说 是你儿子叫我来的
Don't be ridiculous.
别开玩笑了
- I have no son. - That's not true!
- 我没有儿子 - 这不是真的
I know who you are. I've seen the pictures.
我知道你是谁 我见过你的照片
- I was young. I needed the work. - No.
- 我错了 我需要那份工作 - 不
At Mrs. Norris's house.
是诺里斯太太的房子
I didn't know whose house it was.
我不知道是谁的房子
They drugged me. Never mind that.
他们给我吃药 现在已经不重要了
You're outsiders. The council will decide your fates.
你们是外来者 议会会决定你们的命运
The question of the outsiders is now at hand.
我们有外来者的问题
But first, Martha, have you some tidings?
不过首先 玛撒有什么要报告的吗
Nathaniel Winston and Alice Smith
纳撒尼尔 温斯顿和艾丽丝 史密斯
have informed me of their intentions.
告诉了我他们的意图
He intends to have sex with her as soon as possible.
他想尽快和她发生性关系
She intends to put up a mild fight and then give in.
她想稍微反抗一下然后放弃
Amos, something does trouble you?
阿摩司 你有什么烦恼
We now have a majority of those who wish to say "I'm"...
我们这大多数人说"俺"
instead of"I am."
不说"我"
- I'm for that. - I am against it.
- 俺同意这么说 - 我反对
Silence!
安静
We have more important matters to discuss.
我们有更重要的事情讨论
I fear that the presence of the outsiders
我恐怕外人的出现
will attract those of whom we do not speak.
会吸引那些我们没说的人
If you talk about those of whom we do not speak...
如果你谈到那些我们没说的人
have you not spoken of that
你没有说到那些
about which we do not talk?
我们没谈的人吧
Do not speak of that of about which
不要说到那些
we talk of not speaking... about.
我们谈到的没说到
Elder Hale. We should welcome the outsiders among us.
赫尔长者 我们应该欢迎我们中间外来的人
Jeremiah, ought not your tongue be held?
耶利米 你舌头就不应该折起来吗
I am sorry, Elder Hale...
对不起 赫尔长者
but sometimes my tongue wiggles beyond my ability to control it.
但有时我的舌头不随我的意愿摆动
This is a problem with which I have had much experience.
我对这个问题很有经验
Maybe I could help him in a room in which there are no others.
也许我可以在没有别人的房间里帮他
Or you can all watch. I don't give a shit.
你们都可以看着 我才不鸟
Silence.
安静
After this, how about you take your thing of which we do not speak...
这之后 把你那不能说出来的东西
and slide it up in my place of which I like-
滑进我想要的地方怎么样
Silence!
安静
The elders will consult.
长者会商议的
Ah. Much better.
啊 好多了
I'm not in my house, am I?
我没在我的房间是吧
No.
没在
Outsiders, we have decided to let you stay with us...
外来的 我们决定让你待在我们中间
so that you'll be safe from those from of whom we do not-
这样你就远离我们不想 的威胁了
Or don't.
或者说不要
Speak.
说
But now that you are a part of our village...
但既然你是我们村的一份子
understand this:
你要明白
You may never leave.
你永不能离开
No! No!
不 不
How did your son die?
你儿子怎么死的
- The fate of the world is at stake. - You know what to do.
- 世界的命运危在旦夕 - 你知道该怎么办
Was it you? Did you kill him?
是你吗 是你杀了他
This is some shit up with which we will not put.
我们不该被这样对待的
- I'm for that. - I am against it.
- 俺同意 - 我反对
This village isn't what it used to be.
这村子不是原来的样子了
Just hours after the devastating alien attack...
就在毁灭性的外星人攻击几小时后
world leaders have gathered at the United Nations.
世界元首聚集在联合国
In this, mankind's darkest hour...
在这人类最黑暗的时刻
the human race has turned, as one...
人类同心同力
to the wisdom and leadership
寄希望于
of the President of the United States.
美国总统的智慧和领导才能
Ladies and gentlemen, the President of the United States.
女士们先生们 美国总统
Go get 'em, tiger.
你去吧
They mean you, sir.
他们说的是你
Oh, yes, of course.
哦 当然
So... an Indian, a Frenchman and the Pope are all on a plane.
那么 印度人 法国人 和教皇在一架飞机上
The pilot says, "Hey, are any of you not circumcised?"
飞行员说"你们有人没割包皮吗"
So the Pope lifts up his robe and says...
教皇就掀起袍子说
"Shut up, stupid. You don't even speak English."
"闭嘴 笨蛋 你不会讲英语"
The Israeli asked theJapanese guy to open his eyes...
以色列人让日本人睁开眼
but theJapanese man says, "I'm not squinting, you craxyJew.
但是日本人说"我没斜眼 你个犹太疯子"
You're the one who sold me these cheap glasses."
你就是卖给我这便宜眼镜的人
What's the difference between a Belgian and a lump of dog shit?
比利时人和一坨狗屎有什么区别
The Belgian drinks wine, but the dog shit smells good.
比利时人喝酒 但是狗屎气味不错
But, on a serious note, I'm here today at the, uh...
但 说点严肃的 我今天在这里
"un"... because the Earth has been attacked.
"UN"因为地球遭受攻击
I'm happy to report that we may have found a way to fight back.
我很高兴报告我们已经发现了反击的办法
My military advisers at the Pentagram
我在五角大楼的军事顾问
have managed to do the impossible.
可以完成不可能的任务
They have captured one of the alien heat ray guns.
他们已经缴获一把外星热射线枪
As you know, the heat ray destroys the body, leaving behind nothing but clothes.
你们知道 热射线毁掉身体 只留下衣服
Our engineers have managed to reverse the polarity of the weapon
我们的工程师成功地改变了 武器的极性
in the hopes that it can now be turned against
希望这样我们能
the alien invaders.
对抗外星侵略者
Well, where was I?
嗯 我在哪
Ah, yes. We expect that the alien shields will be vulnerable
是的 我们希望外星防护罩是脆弱的
to this reconfigured weapon.
挡不住这重新装配的武器
People, please! Please!
请安静
Please, people. Now, I know that this new technology may seem frightening...
我知道这项新技术看上去吓人
but I believe that deep down inside this heat cannon
但我相信这热枪
is our best chance.
是我们最好的机会
Let me give you a demonstration.
我给你们演示一下
Now let's see if this thing is plugged in.
先看看这东西插进去没有
Uh... it's not a very pretty sight.
里面很美观
Everything's loose and flapping around.
都松了 上下晃动
Look at this little pink thing.
看看这粉色的小东西
Someone get some lubricant, and we'll slather it around in here.
拿点润滑油来 在这多涂点
There.
这
Harper. Good God, these people are all naked.
哈珀 天啊 这些人都裸体了
Have you no shame? Have you no decency?
你不觉得羞耻吗 你不懂礼仪吗
- Sir, you're naked, too. - I am?
- 先生 你也是裸体的 - 是吗
- I thought this was a wrinkly leather coat. - Sir!
- 我以为这是有皱纹的皮革大衣 - 先生
- These aren't buttons? - No!
- 没有纽扣吗 - 没有
I've been pulling this thing up and down like a xipper.
我拉着这东西上上下下像拉链
Mr. President, please.
总统先生 这边
There goes that duck again.
又来了
Yo, man, you see this red weed?
伙计 看见这红草了吗
Nope.
没有
Dad, how much further till Mom's?
爸 还要多久到妈那
I don't know.
不知道
I'm not sure how much longer I can carry your sister.
我不知道还要抱着你妹妹多久
I've been walking this entire time.
我一直在走
- Then who the hell is... - I'll pay you.
- 那这他妈是谁 - 我会付你钱的
Stay close, Rachel.
挨近点 雷切尔
Dad, look!
爸爸 看
Hey! Hey! You guys! I want to help!
嘿 我要去帮忙
Robbie! Oh, no.
罗比 不要
Don't move. For God's sake, stay right there. I'll be right back!
别动 待在这 我马上回来
Hey! Hey, you guys! I want to help.
嘿 我要去帮忙
Awesome!
厉害
- Wait! - Are you craxy?
- 等等 - 你疯了
No! They'll pay for half my college.
不 他们要为我一半大学生活付出代价
Kick ass.
杀啊
Robbie!
罗比
- Yes! - What's the matter with you?
- 太好了 - 你怎么了
Hey, look at that guy. This is so cool!
嘿 看这家伙 真酷
Robbie! Robbie!
罗比 罗比
Rachel! Rachel!
雷切尔 雷切尔
Little girl, are you alone?
小女孩 你一个人
You need to come with me.
你可以和我走
I'll keep you safe, right, kids?
我会保护你的安全 对吧孩子们
Uh-uh.
嗯
- Do you have a little brother? - Get away from her!
- 你又小弟弟吗 - 离她远点
Run away, kids!
快跑 孩子们
Toward the tripod, if you have to!
如果不得不 向三脚架那边去
Don't go! I've got a Ferris wheel and a chimp...
别走 我有观览车 大猩猩
and a big, soft bed we can all get in.
还要大的软床 我们可以都上去
No, please!
不要
Not my real face!
不是我的真脸
No!
不
Over here.
这边
Follow me to safety.
跟我到安全的地方去
- Ow! - Follow me to safety.
- 哦 - 跟我到安全的地方去
- I don't know about this. - I'm an excellent judge of character.
- 我不认识 - 我对角色判断很有一套
All right. Yeah.
好
That's it.
就这样
Oh, Brenda.
哦 布伦达
Yes! You did it!
太好了 你成功了
You have learned quickly and produced splendid butter.
你学做上好奶油很快啊
Are you sure you have not churned before?
你确定前面没搅过吗
Well, we don't call it churning where I come from.
我们那里不叫"搅动"
Pee-pee vagina.
小BB
Quick! Into the cellar.
快 进地下室
No!
不
This is the cellar. That's the cesspool.
这边是地下室 那边是污水池
Damn it!
靠
Quick!
快
Boogedy-boogedy-boogedy.
波波－波波－波波
Boogedy-boogedy-boogedy-boogedy.
波波－波波－波波－波波
Hey! You're not monsters.
嘿 你们不是怪物
Old Lady Henderson?
亨德森大妈
And Pig-FaceJoe!
还要大脸乔
What happened?
怎么回事
It is Henry.
是亨利
He has suffered a heart attack
他心脏病发作了
brought on by this knife.
由这把刀引起
Who did this?
谁干的
It was... Exekiel.
是
Henry, you need a hospital.
亨利 你得去医院
It's not too late. We can help you.
还不是太晚 我们能救你
Perhaps you could start by not leaning on the knife.
也许你得从不压在刀上开始
Do not be concerned for him, Cindy.
别管他 辛迪
We have sent our most qualified villager for medicines.
我们已经派了最好的村民去弄药
I am so dead.
我要死了
Please, leave me alone with Cindy and Brenda.
求求你 让我和辛迪和布伦达单独待一会
I have much to tell them.
我有话告诉她们
Listen carefully to me.
仔细听我说
I am not long for this world.
我活不了多久了
- Pussy. - Brenda!
- 脓包 - 布伦达
What? 50 Cent got shot nine times. He's still walking around.
怎么 50分被射中9次 还活着呢
Tell me, Henry, who killed the boy? Was it you?
告诉我 亨利 谁杀了那孩子 是你吗
No, I loved him and his mother very much.
不是 我非常爱他和他的妈妈
I should have been with him when he died.
他死时我应该和他在一起的
It was horrible.
真可怕
What happened? You must tell me.
怎么回事 你必须告诉我
They went to a boxing match.
他们去看了拳击比赛
It was a women's championship title fight.
是女子冠军锦标赛
And there was a terrible accident.
发生了一场可怕的事故
Oh, my God.
哦 天啊
Only in America!
只有在美国
All this time, I've been searching for his killer
我一直在寻找杀死他的凶手
when it was me, Brenda.
然后却是我自己 布伦达
It was all my fault.
都是我的错
Henry, your son told me that if I found his killer...
亨利 你儿子说如果我找到凶手
I would know how to defeat the aliens.
我就会知道怎样打败外星人
And he was right. Don't you see?
他说的是对的 看到了吗
All you have to do is...
你要做的就是…
Who the hell let his ass out of jail?
谁让这烂人从监狱出来的
His brother, the sheriff.
他哥哥 治安长官
Fuckin' "A."
该死的"A"
There you go, sweetie.
好了 亲爱的
We're gonna die, aren't we?
我们会死的 是吗
Hey, nothing's gonna happen to you. I haven't lost anyone yet.
嘿 没事的 我还没失去任何人
- You've lost Robbie. - Except Robbie.
- 你弄丢了罗比 - 除了罗比
None of that matters right now. What's important is that I'm here with you.
现在无所谓 重要的是我现在和你在一起
Try and get some sleep, okay?
尽量睡点觉
Sing me "Lullaby and Good Night"?
给我唱摇篮曲好吗
I don't know that one.
我不会
Sing me "Hushabye Mountain"?
给我唱"静谧小山丘"
I'm sorry, Rachel, I don't that one, either.
对不起 我也不会
You want this money
你想要钱
Then you gotta be a bad bitch
那就要做贱婊子
Shake that ass for a tip if you a bad bitch
贱婊子就能摇摇屁股拿小费
Drop down to the floor if you a bad bitch
贱婊子就能脱衣到地板上
Oh, no, she ain't no ho
不 她不是
She a bad... bitch
贱婊子
Hey. Come on in.
嘿 进来
Have a seat.
坐
- The name's Oliver. - Tom Ryan.
- 我名叫奥利弗 - 汤姆 赖安
I found this place. Plenty of food-
我发现了这个地方 有充足的食物
Along with two freshly killed busybodies upstairs...
还有两具刚刚被杀死的尸体
who "owned" the place. We could stay here forever.
他们原来是这地方的主人 我们要永远待在这
- Are you afraid? - Of course I'm afraid.
- 你怕吗 - 当然
I'm not. I've been around death plenty.
我不怕 我在死亡边缘很多次了
I used to drive an ambulance in the city...
我以前在城里开救护车
but, apparently, I wasn't a very strong driver.
但是 很明显 我不是个坚强的司机
It seems I was killing more people than I was saving.
看上去我杀死的人比救的人多
Something about that siren got me excited.
警报声让我兴奋
Wham! Carnage.
打 屠杀
But this is different. This is a war.
但现在不一样 这是场战争
No, it's an extermination.
不 这是灭绝
It's no more of a war than there's a war between men and maggots...
这还不如人类和蛆虫的战争
or dragons and wolves...
或者龙和狼的战争
or men riding dragons, throwing wolves at maggots.
或者人类骑着龙 把狼扔向蛆虫的战争
Damn it, Tom. Can't you understand what I'm trying to tell you?
靠 汤姆 你明白我的意思吗
These aliens must have a weakness.
这项外星人一定有弱点
I heard that theJaps killed a few of'em over in Kikkoman.
我听说日本人用酱油杀死了一些
Kikkoman. That's-That's soy sauce.
酱油 就是一种调料
Right, yeah. Low sodium.
对 低钠的
What I'm trying to say, Tom, is that you and I should be fighting these things.
我要说的是 汤姆 是你和我应该去抗争
It's us that should be coming up from under the ground.
是我们应该从地下出来
Of course, we'll have to bury ourselves first...
当然 我们可能会先要牺牲
but it'll be worth it.
但是是值得的
Cool breexe. No sunblock. Worms.
清爽的微风 没有防晒霜 蠕虫
When we build our own tripods, they'll have four legs.
我们建立起自己的三脚架时 他们就四条腿了
I gotta show ya something.
我给你看样东西
We'll tunnel up from behind and scare the piss out of'em.
我们从挖地道过去吓死它们
Wish we had some shovels, don't you?
但愿有更多铁铲
Dad.
爸爸
Daddy!
Rachel!
雷切尔
Rachel! Rachel!
雷切尔 雷切尔
What's the secret, Brenda? What am I missing?
秘密是什么 我错过了什么
Oh, please! More fake monsters?
哦 拜托 还有假怪物
Cindy!
辛迪
Help! Help!
救命 救命
I promised I'd find you, didn't I?
我发誓要找到你的
Where are we? What is this?
我们在哪 这是什么
Some kind of basket attached to the tripod.
连在三脚架上的篮子
Jesus!
天啊
I know, it's horrible. But why?
我知道 很可怕 可是为什么
What are the aliens gonna do to us?
外星人要把我们怎么样
I don't know, but they're taking everyone...
不知道 但是它们什么人都要…
young, old, rich, poor, Chingy.
小的 老的 富的 穷的 还有吓人的
- Daddy! - Rachel!
- 爸爸 - 雷切尔
- No! - Daddy! Help!
- 不 - 爸爸 救命
Tom!
汤姆
Am I dead?
我死了吗
You're not dead.
你没死
- Brenda! - Cindy!
- 布伦达 - 辛迪
Hey... could be worse.
嘿 还有更糟的
- You want to switch? - Okay.
- 你想换换 - 好啊
Brenda, look!
布伦达 看
I don't believe it! The aliens killed a dinosaur!
我不信 外星人杀死了恐龙
Hello, humans. Welcome to the inside of the command tripod.
你好 人类 欢迎到三角指挥部内部
Where's Rachel? What have you done with my daughter?
雷切尔呢 你把我女儿怎么样了
All in good time, Tom. But first, I want to play a game.
她很好 汤姆 但首先 我要做个游戏
The devices you wear will trigger in 60 seconds.
你们戴着的机关60秒后启动
The switch on the wall behind Cindy will disable them.
辛迪身后的墙上的开关可以关掉它们
But where is the key?
但钥匙在哪
I'll give you a hint, Cindy.
我给你个提示 辛迪
Let the game begin.
游戏开始了
I... I don't get it.
我不明白
Okay... maybe this will help you "see."
好吧 也许这个能帮你看见
You want me to... cut something?
你要我切东西
That should be obvious, yes.
很明显 是的
No.
不
No!The key is behind your eye, okay?
不 钥匙在你眼睛后 明白
Zoltar, get in here! This one's gonna do it!
佐达 过来看看 这个人要动手了
Fake eye.
假眼
Bad bar fight in '96.
96年比赛时落下的
Oh.
哦
Oh... oh, I hope this doesn't come between us.
哦 我希望这不影响我们的关系
Of course not.
当然不影响
Is it too late for me to try this on?
我试试这个还来得及吗
Silence! The game is not yet over.
安静 游戏还没结束
- Rachel! - Daddy!
- 雷切尔 - 爸爸
The only thing keeping your children alive, Tom, is you.
汤姆 只有你能让你的孩子活着
Well, we had a good run.
我们命悬一线了
Ha! You weren't expecting that, were you?
你没想到吧
On the contrary, I was counting on it.
相反 在掌握中
I call it... "the nutcracker."
我称之为"胡桃钳"
Why?
为什么
Of course.
当然
Tempura. Sushi. Sashimi!
天麸罗 寿司 生鱼片
Oh, my- Oh, my gosh.
天啊
Of course. Follow the blood. Henry was his stepdad.
当然 按血缘关系 亨利是后爹
You're the little boy's real father!
你才是那小孩真正的父亲
Where did you even meet her?
你什么时候见她的
It was spring break in Cabo. So what?
在卡波春游的时候 那又怎样
I blended in. Seriously, who gives a crap?
我搅进去了 严肃地说 谁他妈关心
What's this?
这是什么
Enjoy your purple nurple, Tom.
享受你的紫奶头吧 汤姆
Please, your son wouldn't want this.
求求你 你儿子不想这样
His soul walks the Earth because of the pain you've caused him.
他的阴魂不散就因为你给他痛苦
No. I have crossed a galaxy for revenge.
不 我跨过银河系来报仇
But it's my fault. Let the others go.
是我的错 放过别人吧
Oh, I don't think so. Look upon him as he writhes!
我不这么想 看着他挣扎吧
Hey, Cindy! Look, I'm on TV, y'all! Check it out!
嘿 辛迪 看 我上电视了
I'm gonna give a shout out to all my peeps!
我要向所有偷窥我的人大喊
Have you lost your mind?
你疯了
No one... bitch slaps... Brenda!
没哪个贱人敢打布伦达
Zoltar, help!
佐达 救命
Oh, oh! This is some bullshit!
哦 真是胡说八道
I know you hold a grudge against humanity for your son's death, but-
我知道你因为你儿子的死 对人类下了咒怨
Oh, wet willy!
哦 靠
Killing us won't bring your little boy back.
杀死我们不会让你儿子回来
No. You will all pay for what you have done.
不 你要为你做的负责
Besides, I've already built this thing.
除此之外 我做了这个东西
When the trap closes on you, it will lock the chain in place.
这装置在你身上关上时 会锁住链条
Your children will be saved...
你的孩子会得救
but you will suffer a terrible death.
但是你死得很惨
Can you hang on to the ones you love?
你会为你爱的人坚持吗
You have 60 seconds.
你有60秒
- No. - Don't worry, kids. I won't quit on you.
- 不 - 别担心 孩子 我不会离开的
It's okay to let go, Dad.
可以走了 爸爸
All you ever had to do was show that you loved me.
你做的显示出你爱我
And show me what it means to be a man.
告诉我你是真的男人
And show me that I could love again.
还告诉我我可以再爱一次
We forgive you, Dad.
我们原谅你 爸爸
The spikes- they stopped!
钉子 它们停了
- Kids! - Daddy!
- 孩子们 - 爸爸
Are you... sparing our lives?
你在拿我们的命开玩笑
Anyone can hold a grudge...
任何人都可以有咒怨
but it takes real courage to forgive.
但是宽恕需要真的勇气
- The invasion is over. - And?
- 侵略结束了 - 还有呢
And I guess I'm sorry or something. I don't know.
我猜我要道个歉什么的 我不知道
Like you mean it.
看来你是真的
Okay.
好
I'm sorry for killing millions of people. Whatever!
对不起杀死了上百万人 差不多啦
Wait... where's Brenda?
等等 布伦达呢
What?
干什么
We're at peace now. I was just sealing the deal.
现在和平了 我刚才在签协议
Come on, Brenda. Let's go.
来吧 布伦达 我们走
Bye, Zoltar! Don't lose my number!
再见 佐达 别丢了我的号码
Tell me you didn't catch something.
告诉我你没捉到什么
Nah, it's cool. She said she was a virgin.
不 很爽 她说她是处女
We are so fucked.
我们太惨了
Mommy!
妈妈
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey, look, kids, Grandpa.
嘿 看 孩子们 是外公
No, that's my new husband.
不 那是我的新老公
Oh, I think it's romantic- the way love can find anyone.
我觉得很浪漫 爱可以找到任何人
And so, love triumphed in the end...
最后 爱取得了胜利
and the invaders were destroyed.
侵略者被打败了
For this world, our world...
对这个世界 我们的世界
is the world of man.
是人之世界
We have earned the right to live here...
我们赢得了住在这的权力
and as long as we love, humanity will prevail.
只要我们爱 人道会盛行的
Each of our enemies has failed in their quest to defeat us...
我们的敌人没能打败我们
each has been undone by their own nefarious plans.
每个都受阻于它们自己的邪恶计划
Among all worlds, across all galaxies...
在全世界 全银河系
we stand above, we stand alone.
我们屹立不倒
None can threaten our existence, none can challenge our spirit.
没人能威胁我们的生存 没人能挑战我们的精神
And why?
为什么
Of all the qualities that make us unique...
所有的品质让我们独一无二
it is love that is our greatest strength...
爱是我们伟大的力量
and because of love, mankind-
因为爱 人类
Thank you. Hello, and welcome to the show.
谢谢 大家好 欢迎来到节目
We have got a very special man with some very special news.
我们这次有特殊嘉宾带来特殊新闻
That's right- he's in the building! The man who saved the world!
是的 他在这大楼里 这个人拯救了世界
Put your hands together for Tom Ryan!
让我们欢迎汤姆 赖安
- Yes! - My best friend.
- 耶 - 我最好的朋友
Whoo!
喔
- Wow. - That's it?
- 喔 - 就这样
Okay.
好
- So, you're in love. - I am. I'm in love.
- 那么 你恋爱了 - 是的
He's lost it. The boy's lost it.
他错过了 这小伙子错过了
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
耶
- You are adorable when you are in love. - Thank you.
- 你恋爱时很可爱 - 谢谢
- Tell us all about her. - She's great. She's really terrific.
- 说说她 - 她很棒 真的
So it's complicated.
那么很复杂
Yeah, you were saying that-that she's complex, I guess.
你是说她很复杂 我想
Shut up!
闭嘴
- Ow! - You're insane. Tom Ryan is insane!
- 哦 - 你疯了 汤姆 赖安疯了
- I'm insane! - Are you happy?
- 我疯了 - 你高兴吗
- You're happy? - I'm so happy. Hey! Look!
- 你高兴 - 我很高兴 嘿 看
Whoa!
哇
Tom. Okay, you've got balls.
汤姆 好的 你有种
Yeah!
耶
Shoe!
鞋
I love Cindy Campbell!
我爱辛迪 坎贝尔
I can jump on things!
我能跳到东西上
Whoa!
哇
Ya-ha! Whoa!
喔
Okay, um, Tom... isn't Cindy here?
好 汤姆 辛迪在这吗
I know she's here. Cindy, I know you're in the building.
我知道她在这 辛迪 我知道你在这
- Cindy! Cindy! - Cindy! Cindy!
- 辛迪 辛迪 - 辛迪 辛迪
- Let's bring her out right now! - I love this woman! I love this woman!
- 我们把她请出来 - 我爱这个女人 我爱这个女人
Oh, God! God!
天啊
Oh, God!